23 24 25
Ei!
Pass
28 29 30
It's getting hot.
I was just saying that.
Pause.
Thirty-one.
He took it.
Yay.
I hate this guy.
That's what I'm talking about.
Here we go.
Who wants to go first?
Yuzu first?
I'll go first.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
11 12 13
14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22
Twenty-three.
Pass
Oh, no.
Oh, what?
Because 30.
30, so next time, if you can say this much more...
Pass.
31!
Yeah!
I really didn't use that!
I didn't use it!
It's the same as the first one!
That's it!
That's not fair, that's not fair.
It's the rat's fault.
I knew it.
Aira-chan's quiz.
Oh!
I'm going to let you win.
Oh, I declare victory
I win already
If I win
Please send me 31
Heh.
Small
Kids
Soybeans
Or vanilla.
No, Daimago Azuki Beans
Delicious, though.
Moka Suzuki's mom likes Daimago Azuki Beans
Hey.
This time I really like Dainago azuki so much that I choose it as my first item
I'm really sorry for the insult.
I think I'm a little bit confused now that I've done something
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll write something about Aira.
It's OK.
Don't look, don't look.
No, don't look at them.
Don't look at me, you two, turn around.
Okay.
Don't look! Turn to your right! You too!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Are you having fun?
I feel like...
Okay, now that I've written it, I'd like to begin.
Let the YES Aira-chan games begin!
How many times was the limit? 30 or 5?
Is it
Is it an impersonation or a gag?
No, it's not. Is it food?
No.
Is it related to a habit?
No. Does it have to do with appearance?
Does it have to do with appearance?
No. It is not a habit.
It's not a habit, and not the other way around.
The food is different, the appearance is different.
There was no airakira at all.
Aira, it had something to do with it, but it was there.
Yes, it was.
But I might be related to what you like. You don't have everything in that line, do you? Shall we go that way?
Here you go.
Is it something to do with the games you like to play?
Play...
Um, yes.
Are there a lot of people who like it?
No.
What, no? I've been thinking about it for a while.
Hey, Yuzumi.
Yuzumi!
It's a game, a game of hesitation. So it's not play.
What, but it's a bit like that, isn't it? That's what it means.
Is this something Aira does well? It is.
What? I don't know, I don't know. It's a game we play a lot, but not many people like it.
What was the last question? Do you do this a lot, Aira? Aira. But I don't know anything about it.
Well, do you play it at home?
Yes.
What?
I know.
Aira does it a lot at home, and nobody likes it much, right?
So, I can only pull one more.
That's for sure.
That's not good.
You mean two, right?
Yes, that's right.
Yuzuki thought of one.
I can't think of anything I can do at home.
It's strange that you guys are doing it and not many people are around.
There are only a limited number of things you can do at home.
That's for sure.
You don't have many people you like, do you?
I don't know about that.
The things we do at home are just switches and myofascial rollers,
Switch and myofascial roller are the only things we often do at home.
Izuki, I thought you were watching Kanoueiko's horror YouTube.
So, you want to focus on someone who is related to that?
I'm not sure. Like Doremi-chan.
What?
Tell me, don't watch it, don't watch it.
We've come this far, and it's not gonna stop.
Oops.
Whoa, you're not so lucky.
Let's just get up. I'm not getting up.
Don't cooperate. Don't cooperate. Don't cooperate.
Come on, I'll get up. I'm not happy.
Don't cooperate. Don't cooperate.
Go ahead, get up. I don't need it. I'll get up.
You should think about it.
What? I don't know.
Is this something you're doing on your own, Ira?
Yes.
Do you want me to put it on YouTube?
Is that something Ira is watching?
NO.
Done.
But I definitely want to do a gold leaf roller.
Gold leaf roller or painting?
I would like you to present the answer you have narrowed down.
Let's start with me.
Here is the answer I came up with.
Jang.
Fight with parents. I don't know, there may be a lot of people who fight with their parents for sure,
But there is only one person who fights with Ira's mom and dad. So, I think that many people don't fight with their parents,
I said that I like to see Isla fighting with her parents,
So, Ira when they are fighting.
He said something like he likes to be moved, so I wondered if he sees those fights as playful.
I see. I was a little confused, that's for sure. That's what I thought, so I decided to do this. I'm out of sync with other people's sensibilities.
I was going to write something like that before, but I decided not to.
Everything was different, and I was already in a strange place.
I see.
Then I'll write the lyrics.
I'll write the lyrics. When I was staying at Aira's house, she would ask me to write some lyrics,
Aira often comes up with lyrics. She's a romantic. Isn't that how you feel? We used to make a song together at Amehera.
I've seen her thinking about it happily when we asked her to come up with lyrics for a song we were going to write.
There aren't many people who like to write songs, so I thought it would be a good idea to give it a try. So I thought it might be a good idea to give it a try.
It's private, so there might be a kind of playfulness in it.
Here is the correct answer. Ta-da!
Aira's towel!
Huh? Huh?
Where's Alovey?
I'm sorry. It was thrown away.
Yes, it's gone now.
He hasn't been around for about a year.
He said his mom threw him out.
That's a lie!
No one like that.
So, no one.
None. No one dumped me.
No, no, no, none. You talk about it a lot.
No, no, no, that was a year ago.
Is that a problem? Like, nothing is good now.
Right. I didn't know that rule.
This is, uh, Ira's towel.
For those of you who don't know.
Isla had a bath towel, like a comforter, that she'd had since she was a baby.
She loved it and used it a lot.
And when he grew up, he still had these scraps.
She used to bring it with her to hotels and such.
He used to talk about it a lot.
He used to talk about it like a member of the group.
We used to talk about how good the fiber was.
You always said you like to get into it like this and do it like this.
You said you liked to play with it.
So I decided to go with that.
Well, he threw it away about a year ago, so...
So, no.
No?
This is the final battle.
I don't care what you've been doing.
The game you're not allowed to show your face in.
I'm already on it.
Well, then, you're in a great mood. I don't think I'm going to make it.
Are you okay? Let's do this.